Contact

0468 305 887 (Mobile) dworkmang@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ danielworkman1 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Digital Marketing
Digital Project Management
Website Design

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Bachelor of Commerce

Daniel Workman

Digital Development Manager at COG Branding Greater Sydney Area

Summary

Experienced Digital Producer with a demonstrated history of working in the marketing and advertising industry. Skilled in Digital Marketing, Digital Project Management and Website Design. Strong media and communication professional graduated from The University of Sydney Business School.

Experience

COG Branding 3 years 2 months

Digital Development Manager August 2020 - Present (4 months)

Sydney, New South Wales, Australia

The primary focus of my role is leading a team of developers and designers in the production of digital technologies.

My roll encompasses Digital Project Management and Website Development using CMS platforms such as Wordpress, Magento, Shopify, & BigCommerce.

Mid Digital Producer October 2019 - August 2020 (11 months) Sydney, Australia

An experienced Digital Producer managing Digital Projects across Digital Marketing and Website Development.

My role requires requires expert language and communication skills as it is managing a team in-house and also client facing.

Daily tasks include, but are not limited to:

- Digital Project Management
- SEM: Google Ads / Bing Ads (Strategic Search. Display. & Shopping campaigns)

- SEM: Social Media Campaigns (Facebook, Instagram and LinkedIn)
- Website Design: Magento, Wordpress, Shopify, BigCommerce, & more
- SEO: Website Audits & Redevelopment
- Brand Strategy: Brand Development Workshops
- Email Marketing: Campaign Monitor & Mailchimp
- Copywriting: News & Blog Writing
- Digital Reporting: Google Analytics and Google Data Studio

Digital Producer

October 2017 - October 2019 (2 years 1 month)

Sydney, Australia

My role requires a thorough understanding of Digital Marketing and Website Design. My role also requires expert language and communication skills as it is client facing.

Daily tasks include, but are not limited to:

- SEM: Google Ads / Bing Ads (Strategic Search. Display. & Shopping campaigns)
- SEM: Social Media Campaigns (Facebook, Instagram and LinkedIn)
- Website Design: Magento, Wordpress, Shopify, BigCommerce, & more
- SEO: Website Audits & Redevelopment
- Brand Strategy: Brand Development Workshops
- Email Marketing: Campaign Monitor & Mailchimp
- Copywriting: News & Blog Writing
- Digital Reporting: Google Analytics and Google Data Studio

- Digital Project Management: Running a small team of Web Developers & Designers

Sustainable Future Group Marketing Assistant June 2017 - October 2017 (5 months) Sydney, Australia

Sustainable Future Group is an Australian owned organisation, focused on reducing operational costs and environmental impacts.

My responsibilities include but are not limited to:

- EDM campaigns, using Mailchimp software
- CMS Wordpress / WIX website design & maintenance
- SEO analysis & implementation
- Creating branding strategies
- Creating marketing strategies
- Writing digital marketing content
- Writing social media content
- Creating Webinar & workshop presentations, using powerpoint
- Working with client in-house marketing, public relations and communications experts to create content and marketing collateral

Vibe Teacher Recruitment Teaching Assistant October 2015 - July 2016 (10 months)

London, United Kingdom

Work consisted of monitoring and assisting children with learning difficulties, physical disabilities and severe behavioural issues.

Rydges Hotels & Resorts Bartender 2011 - 2014 (3 years)

Sydney, Australia

Some responsibilities included:

- Consumer service the importance of handling each customer as an individual and always remain diligent when handling complaints
- Working in teams knowing that everyone has strengths and weaknesses and to utilise people best by assigning them tasks based on these

• Team player – working important functions on my birthday and Christmas.

Although I would have liked these times off, I realised that you need to put your job first when they are relying on you.

Education

Coder Academy

Diploma of Information Technology, Computer Software Engineering · (2020 - 2021)

The University of Sydney Business School
Agile Project Management & Design Thinking · (2017 - 2017)

University of Wollongong
Bachelor's Degree, Commerce / Marketing · (2011 - 2014)

The Scots College

High School Certificate (2007 - 2010)